 export let questions = [
    {
        question : "The Brain of any computer system is?",
        options :["Memory", "CPU","ALU","CU"],
        answer : 2
    }, {
        question : "Full-Form of CPU.",    
        options :["Centre process unit", "Central Processing Unit"," Central Processor Unit",
        "  None of these"],
        answer : 2
    }, {
        question : "What is the Extension of Adobe Reader ?",  
        options :["PDF", "RTF","PPT","PCF"],
        answer : 1
    }, {
        question : "What is a full form of CD?",
        options :["Compact disk", "Common disk","Compact directory","Compact drive"],
        answer : 1
    }, {
        question : " Who is the father of the Computer?",
        options :[" Dennis richie", " Tim crooks","Arnald macy","Charls bebej"],
        answer : 4
    }, {
        question : "HTML stand for?",
        options :[" Hyper text transfer Language", " Hyphen text marked Language","Hyper text markup Language","Hyper text transfer Lacality"],
        answer : 3
    }, {
        question : " The standard protocol of the Internet is ?",
        options :["TCP/IP", "Https"," www","Ftp"],
        answer : 1
    },  {
        question : "Full-Form of CPU.",    
        options :["Centre process unit", "Central Processing Unit"," Central Processor Unit",
        "  None of these"],
        answer : 2
    }, {
        question : "What is the Extension of Adobe Reader ?",  
        options :["PDF", "RTF","PPT","PCF"],
        answer : 1
    },
    {
        question : "HTML stand for?",
        options :[" Hyper text transfer Language", " Hyphen text marked Language","Hyper text markup Language","Hyper text transfer Lacality"],
        answer : 3
    },
]